https://www.sigmaomegaomega.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
The Sigma Omega Omega Chapter of Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority, Inc. is committed and recognizes your need for protection and privacy issues on the Internet.
In general, you can visit us at www.sigmaomegaomega.com without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. We do collect the Internet Protocol (IP) addresses and domain names of visitors for site administration purposes, such as to analyze this for trends and statistics. No personal information is obtained, rather just the patterns of usage of our various users may be tracked and monitored. This data is used to customize our website content to deliver a better experience to our users.
Collecting Personally Identifiable Information
There are times when we may collect personal information from you. For example, in order to respond to your questions or fulfill your requests, it may be necessary to ask for personal information such as your name, address, e-mail address and telephone number. We may use this information to respond to your requests, or to contact you via mail, e-mail or phone to inform you of events or announcements regarding our chapter. We will not provide this information to a third party without your permission, except as necessary to fulfill your request.
Links to Other Websites
Sigma Omega Omega Chapter’s website may contain links to other sites. These sites are not controlled by Sigma Omega Omega Chapter and Sigma Omega Omega Chapter is not responsible for any content contained on any such website. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by other sites. As with our site, you should become familiar with any external party’s privacy policy when visiting that site.
Your Consent
By using the website of Sigma Omega Omega Chapter of the Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority, Inc., you consent to our use of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time without advance notice. Should any new policy go into effect, we will post it on this site, and the policy will apply only to information connected thereafter.
Disclaimers
THIS WEBSITE AND ITS CONTENT ARE PROVIDED “AS IS” AND SIGMA OMEGA OMEGA CHAPTER EXCLUDES TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAW ANY WARRANTY, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, SATISFACTORY QUALITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. THE FUNCTIONS EMBODIED ON, OR IN THE MATERIALS OF, THIS WEBSITE ARE NOT WARRANTED TO BE UNINTERRUPTED OR WITHOUT ERROR. YOU, NOT SIGMA OMEGA OMEGA CHAPTER, ASSUME THE ENTIRE COST OF ALL NECESSARY SERVICING, REPAIR OR CORRECTION DUE TO YOUR USE OF THIS WEBSITE.
Except as specifically stated in this Policy, or elsewhere on this website, or as otherwise required by applicable law, neither Sigma Omega Omega Chapter nor its members, content providers, or other representatives will be liable for damages of any kind (including, without limitation, lost profits, direct, indirect, compensatory, consequential, exemplary, special, incidental, or punitive damages) arising out of your use of, your inability to use, or the performance of this website or the Content whether or not we have been advised of the possibility of such damages.
Sigma Omega Omega chapter uses reasonable efforts to ensure the accuracy, correctness and reliability of the content, but we make no representations or warranties as to the content’s accuracy, correctness or reliability.
Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority, Inc. is not responsible for the design nor content of these web pages. They are the sole property and responsibility of the Sigma Omega Omega Chapter who hosts and maintains this website.
Some U.S. states and foreign countries do not permit the exclusion or limitation of implied warranties or liability for certain categories of damages. Therefore, some or all of the limitations above may not apply to you to the extent they are prohibited or superseded by state or international provisions.
Browsers This site is best viewed in Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome, Safari or Opera. Last update on December 1, 2020.
Copyright 2020 Sigma Omega Omega Chapter of Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority, Inc.
